怎么
What?
不好笑吗
Was the joke that bad?
我要杀了你
I'm gonna kill you.
什么
What?
我没听见 你得大声点
I didn't quite catch that. You're gonna have to speak up.
不在今天
Not today…
不在明天
…not tomorrow…
但我要杀了你
…but I'm gonna kill you.
天啊
Jesus.
西蒙
Simon…
他有什么 一把刀吗
what did he have, a knife?
他有一把短斧
Uh, he had a hatchet.
一把短斧
A hatchet?
他有一把斧子
He had an ax.
西蒙是我的左右手
Simon's my right-hand man.
有左右手是很重要的
Having one of those is important.
没了他们 你会剩下什么
I mean, what do you have left without them?
许多工作
A whole lot of work.
你有左右手吗
Do you have one?
也许是这里还活着的一个人
Maybe one of these fine people still breathing?
还是我…
Or did I…
好吧
Sure.
好
Yeah.
把他的斧子给我
Give me his ax.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
也许瑞克会跟我一起回来
Maybe Rick will be with me.
如果没有
And if not, well,
我们可以将他们扒皮抽骨 对吧
we can just turn these people inside out, won't we?
我是说 剩下的人
I mean… the ones that are left.
《行尸走肉》
我们去兜兜风
Let's go for a ride.
真是垃圾
What a piece of shit.
「我要杀了你」
"I'm gonna kill you."
你开玩笑吗
Are you kiddin' me?
你看见刚发生的事了吗 我做的事
Did you see what just happened, what I just did?
你就
You just…
你最好的机会是
Your best chance…
站起来 拿起那把斧子
is to stand up, grab that ax,
砍穿我的后脑勺
and drive it through the back of my head.
看看你怎么做
See how you do.
继续装硬汉
Keep actin' tough.
来吧
Go ahead.
拿起斧子
Grab the damn ax.
放下
Drop it.
别让我再起身
Don't make me get up again.
瞧瞧
Well, look at that.
快破晓了
Dawn is breakin'.
又是全新的一天 瑞克
It's a brand-new day, Rick.
我想要你想想可能发生的事
I want you to think about what could have happened…
想想发生的事
…think about what happened,
想想还可能发生的事
and think about what can still happen.
砰
Boom!
那让你想到你认识的人了吗
That remind you of anybody you know?
是啊
Oh, yeah.
你是我的了
You are mine.
那里的人 他们是我的了
The people back there … they are mine.
这
This…
这也是我的
This is mine.
瑞克
Hey, Rick…
去捡我的斧子
go get my ax.
我们做朋友
Let's be friends.
去捡我的斧子
Get my ax.
我猜你们一定都以为你们会一起变老
Bet you thought you were all gonna grow old together,
周日晚上围坐在桌边一起吃饭
sittin' around the table at Sunday dinner.
从此幸福地生活在一起
and the happily ever after.
不
No.
不是那么回事 瑞克
Doesn't work like that, Rick.
不再是了
Not anymore.
想想发生的事
Think about what happened.
我只是无法决定
I simply cannot decide.
我有个主意
I got an idea.
点
Eenie…
兵
meenie…
点
miney…
将
mo…
骑
catch…
虎
a tiger…
打
by…
仗
his toe.
点到
If…
哪里
he hollers…
哪里就上
let him go.
头
My mother…
破
told me…
血
to pick…
流
the very…
死
best one…
在
and you…
场
are…
上
it.
有人敢动或说话
Anybody moves, anybody says anything,
就把那孩子的另一只眼挖出来喂他父亲吃
cut the boy's other eye out and feed it to his father,
然后我们再开始
and then we'll start.
你可以呼吸 你可以眨眼
You can breathe. You can blink.
你可以哭泣
You can cry.
见鬼 你们每个人都会那样的
Hell, you're all gonna be doing that.
看看
Look at that!
真有种
Taking it like a champ!
给
Suck…
我
my…
滚蛋
nuts.
你们听见了吗
Did you hear that?
他让我滚蛋
He said, "suck my nuts."
老天啊
Oh, my goodness!
看看啊
Look at this!
大家伙儿们 瞧瞧我肮脏的坏女孩
You guys, look at my dirty girl!
小甜心…
Sweetheart…
好好看看
Lay your eyes on this.
该死的
Oh, damn.
你俩…
Were you …
你俩是一对吗
Were you together?
真惨
That sucks.
假如你俩真是一对 你就应该知道
But if you were, you should know.
这一切都是有原因的
there was a reason for all this.
红毛 该死的 他过去是 现在是
Red … and hell, he was, is,
将来也永远会是红的了
and will ever be red.
他为你们团队里的一人 或六人
He just took one or six.
甚至是七人挡了一劫
or seven for the team!
所以 仔细 看看
So take…a damn look.
仔细看看
Take a damn look!
达里尔
Daryl!
不
No!
不行
Oh, no.
那种行为
That?
老天爷
Oh, my!
那种行为
That…
绝对不可取
is a no-no.
这整件事
The whole thing …
绝对不允许出现任何类似的行为
not one bit of that shit flies here.
你想我动手吗
Do you want me to do it?
就地正法
Right here.
不
No.
不 你不能杀了他们
No, you don't kill them…
不能这么轻易地杀了他们
not until you try a little.
话说回来
And anyway…
规矩不是这样的
that's not how it works.
我已经告诉过你们了
Now, I already told you people …
第一次算了
first one's free,
然后我还说了什么来着
then what'd I say?
我说我会弄死你们的
I said I would shut that shit down!
没有例外
No exceptions.
我不知道你们之前都是在和
Now, I don't know what kind of lying assholes.
什么样的骗子打交道
you've been dealing with…
但我是个讲信用的人
…but I'm a man of my word.
第一印象很重要
First impressions are important.
我要你们了解我
I need you to know me.
那么…
So…
重新再来
…back to it.
不
No!
伙计 你还有知觉吗
Buddy, you still there?
我不知道
I just don't know.
好像你想说什么
It seems like you're trying to speak,
但你刚中了一棒
but you just took a hell of a hit.
我砸你脑袋太用力了
I just popped your skull so hard,
你眼球都爆出来了
your eyeball just popped out,
真是恶心死了
and it is gross as shit!
玛姬 我会找到你的
Maggie, I'll find you.
该死的
Oh, hell.
能看出来这对你们来说太残酷了
I can see this is hard on you guys.
我很抱歉
I am sorry.
真心的
I truly am.
但我确实说过
But I did say it.
没有例外
No exceptions!
你们这帮孬种
You bunch of pussies.
我才刚开始
I'm just getting started.
露西尔很饥渴
Lucille is thirsty.
她是根嗜血的球棒
She is a vampire bat.
怎么
What?
不好笑吗
Was the joke that bad?
他们死了 瑞克
People died, Rick.
那确实发生了
It's what happened.
不代表其他人也要去死
Doesn't mean the rest of them have to.
把我的斧子给我
Get me my ax.
把我的 斧子 给我
Get me…my…ax!
我以为你行 瑞克
I thought you were the guy, Rick.
也许你不行
Maybe you're not.
再给你一次机会
We'll give it one more go.
我现在真心希望你再试一下
Now, I really want you to try this time.
最后一次机会
Last chance.
把我的斧子给我
Bring me my ax!
时间不等人 瑞克
Clock is ticking, Rick!
想想还可能发生的事
Think about what can still happen.
真乖
Attaboy!
我们到了 混蛋
We're here, prick.
你一定不好受对吧
This must be hard for you, right?
一直以来你都是最强者
I mean, you have been King Shit for so long.
瞬间失去两个自己人
Losin' two of your own like…
被那样殴杀 一个接着一个
Gettin' 'em clipped like that, one nut, then the other,
还当着你儿子的面
and in front of your boy?
那真是糟透了
That is some screwed-up shit!
太好了
Goody.
你以前是老大
You were in charge.
该死
Hell…
你可能…
…you were probably…
当上瘾了
addicted to it.
现在
And now, well,
啪啪两下 就结束了
clip, clip … that's over.
但是…
But…
你还是可以为我服务
…you can still lead…
过上美好殷实的生活
a nice, productive life producing for me.
我觉得你会需要的
I think you're gonna need it.
我有预感
I just got a feelin'.
那么拿去
So take it.
我们到了
Here we are.
让我问你 瑞克
Let me ask you something, Rick …
你知道那段小旅行的意义吗
do you even know what that little trip was about?
让你说你就说
Speak when you're spoken to.
好的 好的
Okay. Okay.
那旅行的意义
That trip was about.
在于你看我的眼神
at you looked at me.
我想改变你
I wanted to change that.
我想要你明白
I wanted you to understand.
但你还是用那同样该死的眼神看我
But you're still looking at me the same damn way…
就像我在你的煎蛋里拉屎了一样
…like I shit in your scrambled eggs,
那是不行的
and that's not gonna work.
那么…
So…
我要再给你一次机会吗
…do I give you another chance?
要
Yeah.
好的
Yes.
好吧
Okay.
好了
All right.
那就开始吧 超级大奖赛
And here it is … the grand-prize game.
你接下来做出的选择 会决定这糟糕的一天
What you do next will decide whether your crap day.
会变成大家最后糟糕的一天
becomes everyone's last crap day.
还是说只是普通糟糕的一天
or just another crap day.
用枪指着他们的头
Get some guns to the back of their heads.
好 那么…
Good. Now…
和他们鼻子齐平 这样一开枪…
level with their noses, so if you have to fire…
那画面会很惨烈
it'll be a real mess.
孩子
Kid…
过来
Right here.
孩子 快点
Kid…now.
你是左撇子吗
You a southpaw?
什么
Am I a what?
你惯用左手吗
You a lefty?
不
No.
很好
Good.
疼吗
That hurt?
不
No.
你应该疼
Should.
应该觉得疼
It's supposed to.
好了
All right.
趴在地上 孩子 趴在爸爸边上
Get down on the ground, kid, next to Daddy.
展开双手
Spread them wings.
西蒙
Simon…
你有笔吗
…you got a pen?
有
Yeah.
抱歉 孩子
Sorry, kid.
这会凉得像巫师的阴囊
This is gonna be as cold as a warlock's ballsack,
好像他在你上面挺着阴囊
just like he was hanging his ballsack above you.
然后拖过你的前臂
and dragging it right across the forearm.
好了
There you go.
给你留一点
Gives you a little leverage.
求你了 求你了
Please. Please.
求你不要
Please don't.
求我
Me?
我什么都不会干的
I ain't doing shit.
瑞克 我要你拿起斧头
Rick, I want you to take your ax…
砍下你儿子的左臂
cut your son's left arm off,
就顺着那条线
right on that line.
我知道 我知道
Now, I know … I know.
你要花点时间接受这个信息
You're gonna have to process that for a second.
这是正常的
That makes sense.
但是 我还是要你动手
Still, though, I'm gonna need you to do it,
不然其他人就得死
or all these people are gonna die.
然后卡尔也要死
Then Carl dies,
家里的那些人也要死
then the people back home die…
最后 你也得死
and then you, eventually.
我会让你苟活个几年
I'm gonna keep you breathing for a few years,
让你备受煎熬
just so you can stew on it.
你…你不用这么做的
You … you don't have to do this.
我们明白了
We understand.
你明白了
You understand.
是啊
Yeah.
我只是不确定瑞克明不明白
I'm not sure that Rick does.
我要你干脆利落地
I'm gonna need a clean cut.
顺着那条线砍
right there on that line.
我知道这样要求很过分
Now, I know this is a screwed-up thing to ask,
但你得砍成像意大利香肠片一样
but it's gonna have to be like a salami slice …
切口齐整 干净 45度角
nothing messy, clean, 45 degrees …
好让我们缝合伤口
give us something to fold over.
我们有个好医生
We got a great doctor.
孩子不会有事的
The kid'll be fine.
大概吧
Probably.
瑞克
Rick…
必须现在就做
…this needs to happen now …
快点
chop, chop …
不然我亲自砸烂这小子的脑袋
or I will crush the little fella's skull myself.
可以换我
It can … It can … It can be me.
It can be me.
你可以砍我的手
Y-You can do it to me.
我可以跟你走
I c… I can go with … with you.
不行
No.
这是唯一的办法
This is the only way.
瑞克
Rick…
拿起斧子
pick up the ax.
不做决定也是个大决定
Not making a decision is a big decision.
你真想看这些人都死吗
You really want to see all these people die?
你会看到的
You will.
你会看到每个肮脏的细节
You will see every ugly thing.
天啊
Oh, my God.
你要逼我倒数吗
Are you gonna make me count?
好吧 瑞克
Okay, Rick.
你赢了
You win.
我数
I am counting.
- 三 - 求你了
- 3! - Please.
求你了
Please.
可以换我
It can be me.
求你了
Please!
二
2!
求你了 别这样
Please, don't do …
时间要到了
This is it.
一
1.?
爸爸 砍吧
Dad… just do it.
砍吧
Just do it.
瑞克
Rick.
你听我号令
You answer to me.
你向我上贡
You provide for me.
你属于我
You belong to me.
对吗
Right?
让你说你就说
Speak when you're spoken to!
你听我号令
You answer to me.
你向我上贡
You provide for me.
向你上贡
Provide for you.
你属于我 对吗
You belong to me, right?!
对
Right.
很好
这…
That…
就是我想看到的眼神
…is the look I wanted to see.
我们做到了
We did it…
我们所有人 齐心协力
all of us, together…
甚至包括地上趴着的死人
even the dead guys on the ground.
见鬼 他们肯定要得精神奖
Hell, they get the spirit award, for sure.
今天是他妈高效的一天
Today was a productive damn day!
现在我希望 为了你们好
Now, I hope, for all your sake…
你们明白了
that you get it now…
你们理解事情的运作方式
…that you understand how things work.
一切已改变
Things have changed.
不管你们以前怎么样
Whatever you had going for you…
现在都已结束
…that is over now.
德怀特
Ah. Dwight…
拉他上车
…load him up.
他有种
He's got guts …
不像我认识的某个小婊子
not a little bitch like someone I know.
我喜欢他
I like him.
他现在是我的了
He's mine now.
但如果你还想打鬼主意
But you still want to try something?
「不在今天 不在明天」
"Not today, not tomorrow."
"Not today, not tomorrow"?
我会砍下一部分…
I will cut pieces off of…
他叫什么来着
Hell's his name?
达里尔
Daryl.
听上去还挺搭的
That actually sounds right.
我会切下达里尔的一部分
I will cut pieces off of Daryl.
然后放到你的门口
and put them on your doorstep …
或者 更棒的是 我把他带到你面前
or, better yet, I will bring him to you.
让你来替我动手
and have you do it for me.
欢迎来到全新的开始 你们这些可怜虫
Welcome to a brand-new beginning, you sorry shits!
我给你们一辆货车
I'm gonna leave you a truck.
留着吧
Keep it.
用来装你们给我弄到的各种物资
Use it to cart all the crap you're gonna find me.
我们会在一周后来收取第一次的贡品
We'll be back for our first offering in one week.
在那之前
Until then…
再见
ta-ta.
玛姬 玛姬
Maggie. Maggie.
玛姬
Maggie…
你得坐下
you need to sit down.
- 玛姬 - 不
- Maggie. - No.
我们需要把你送去山顶寨
We need to get you to the Hilltop.
你得去做好准备
You need to go get ready.
准备什么
For what?
抗击他们
To fight them.
他们手里有达里尔
They have Daryl.
他们有一支军队
They have an army.
我们会死的 全都会死
We would die … all of us.
回家去吧
Go home.
把大家都带回去
Take everybody with you.
我可以一个人去那里
I can get there by myself.
你站都站不稳了
You can barely stand up.
我必须去
I need to go.
你需要回亚历山大去
You need to go to Alexandria.
你们是为了我才出来的
You were out … out here for me.
我们现在依然是
We still are.
我现在一个人可以去了
I can make it now.
我需要你们回去
I need you to go back.
我不能让你们在外面
I can't have you out here.
我不能再让你们在外面冒险了
I can't have you all out here anymore.
我需要你们回去
I need you to go back.
玛姬
Maggie…
我们不会让你一个人走的
we're not letting you go.
好吗
Okay?
你们必须让我走
You have to.
那是不可能的
It's not gonna happen.
我带着她
I'm taking her.
我会送她去那里的
I'm gonna get her there.
我会保护她的安全
I'm gonna keep her safe.
我由不得你拒绝
I'm not giving you a choice.
我要带着他一起
I'm taking him with me.
我要带上他
I'm gonna take him.
我要这么做
That's what I'm gonna do.
我必须这么做 拜托了
I need to do this. Please.
我们要帮你
We need to help you.
我来吧
I got it.
不 不
No. No.
拜托 让我们帮忙吧
Pl… Pl… Please let us.
他是我们的家人
He… He's our family, t…
他也是我们的家人
He's our family, too.
好了 数到三
All right. On three.
一 二
1, 2…
我猜你们一定都以为你们会一起变老
Bet you thought you were all gonna grow old together,
周日晚上围坐在桌边一起吃饭
sittin' around the table at Sunday dinner.
从此幸福地生活在一起
and the happily ever after.
不
No.
不是那么回事 瑞克
Doesn't work like that, Rick.
不再是了
Not anymore.